questions = [
    {
        "question":"Who composed Piano Sonata No.8?",
        "correctAnswer":"Ludwig Van Beethoven",
        "answer0":"Henry Purcell",
        "answer1":"George Frederic Handel",
        "answer2":"Johann Sebastian Bach"
    },
    {
        "question": "What key is this piece in?",
        "correctAnswer": "C minor",
        "answer0": "E minor",
        "answer1": "D major",
        "answer2": "C major",
    },
    {
        "question": "How does the piece begin which is unusual to a normal sonata?",
        "correctAnswer": "Slow introduction",
        "answer0": "Exposition",
        "answer1": "Forte",
        "answer2": "Fast introduction",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first theme in the exposition called?",
        "correctAnswer": "First Subject",
        "answer0": "Introduction",
        "answer1": "Second Subject",
        "answer2": "Transition",
    },
    {
        "question": "What section is heard last in a sonata?",
        "correctAnswer": "Recapitulation",
        "answer0": "Exposition",
        "answer1": "Development",
        "answer2": "Subjects",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the tempo of the opening?",
        "correctAnswer": "Grave",
        "answer0": "Allegro",
        "answer1": "Andante",
        "answer2": "Presto",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recapitulation?",
        "correctAnswer": "The final section",
        "answer0": "The second section",
        "answer1": "The first section",
        "answer2": "The subjects",
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the first theme of the exposition called?",
        "correctAnswer":"First Subject",
        "answer0":"Recapitulation",
        "answer1":"Introduction",
        "answer2":"First Exposition"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the name of the middle section of a sonata?",
        "correctAnswer":"Development",
        "answer0":"Exposition",
        "answer1":"Slow introduction",
        "answer2":"Recapitulation"
    },
    {
        "question":"What structure is the piece?",
        "correctAnswer":"Sonata form",
        "answer0":"Binary",
        "answer1":"Ternary",
        "answer2":"Arch form"
    },
    {
        "question":"What happens between the 1st and 2nd subject in the exposition?",
        "correctAnswer":"Transition",
        "answer0":"Development",
        "answer1":"Modulation",
        "answer2":"Recapitulation"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the recapitulation?",
        "correctAnswer":"A recap of the exposition",
        "answer0":"A recap of the development",
        "answer1":"A recap of the slow introduction",
        "answer2":"A new section with new themes"
    },
    {
        "question":"What key is transitioned to in the recapitulation that we expected in the exposition?",
        "correctAnswer":"Eb major",
        "answer0":"C major",
        "answer1":"C minor",
        "answer2":"Eb minor"
    },
    {
        "question":"What key is transitioned to in the exposition that we do not expect?",
        "correctAnswer":"Eb minor",
        "answer0":"C minor",
        "answer1":"Eb major",
        "answer2":"C major"
    }
]